1911forum.com 2015-09-11

# 1911Forum - FAQ: Privacy

Untitled Document

### What information do we collect?

Our servers automatically collect information from your browser whenever you visit the site. These server logs may include your Internet Protocol address, cookie information, software and hardware attributes, and the page you request.

We collect information from you when you register on our site. When registering, you may be asked to enter your user name, password, e-mail address, date of birth, location, occupation, as well as any other information that you decide to provide. In an effort to reduce unwanted posts on our site, your user name, email address, and Internet Protocol address is submitted to a third-party service at the time of registration to check for abuse. [Stop Forum Spam](http://www.stopforumspam.com/)'s privacy policy can be viewed [here](http://www.stopforumspam.com/privacy).

We may collect personal information if you post it on the interactive forum, in your account profile, or if you contact us directly. Please do not post any personal information on the forums or in your account profile that you expect to keep private.

### What do we use your information for?

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

  * To personalize your experience. Your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs.
  * To improve our website. We continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you.
  * To improve customer service. Your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs.
  * To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature.
  * To send periodic emails. The email address you provide may be used to send you occasional company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.

### Do we use cookies?

Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.

We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits, keep track of advertisements and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.

### Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

### Third party links

We may include or offer third party products or services on our website. In addition, visitors may post links to third party sites on the interactive forum. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

### Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

In compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

### Online Privacy Policy Only

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

### Terms and Conditions

Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at <http://www.1911forum.com/legal.php>

### Your Consent

By using our site, you consent to our web site privacy policy.

### Changes to our Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will update the Privacy Policy modification date below.

This policy was last modified on 4/1/2011

### Contacting Us

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below:

By email: [webmaster@1911forum.com](mailto:webmaster@1911forum.com)
